<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Regular Expressions Basics</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Coding can be difficult, but you are not alone!  Regular Expressions A regular expression, also known as regex, is a part of Python that is useful for finding matches of specific search patterns.
Regex Symbols These symbols below are used to match any or specific characters! It may seem like it is a lot, but don&#39;t worry! The more you practice, the easier it gets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pushing your website up to GitHub</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/09/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/09/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Pushing your website up to GitHub Just follow these steps to push your website to GitHub!
Go to your terminal
 Type pwd to check your directory. You will get something like /stor/home/ek8435/website/public
 Type git init to initialize the local git repository. You will get something like Initialized empty Git repository in /stor/home/ek8435/website/public/.git/
 Type and run git add .
 Type and run git commit -m &amp;quot;test site&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Reticulate</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/06/using-reticulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/06/using-reticulate/</guid>
      <description>Reticulate Whenever you need R and Python to work together and share information, you can use reticulate.
This is fairly easy!
When you insert a chunck (shortcut: Ctrl+Alt+I OR Command+Option+I), you will see {r}. That means that that chunk will be using R. You can change {r} to {python} to simply switch the chunk to a Python code chunk.
First, you need to run library(reticulate) in the R code chunk to make R and Python communicate with each other!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet My Cat</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/04/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/04/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Meet Louis!   This is my cat, Louis! =^._.^=
 Louis is a yellow tabby cat, and he is 5 years old. He likes to eat, look out the window, groom himself, and sleep.
 He is not the nicest cat, but he has a really pretty voice. He is really soft also.
He used to be an indoor/outdoor cat, but he would dig up our neighbors&#39; gardens that we now have to keep him inside :( He would still try to run out the door whenever he gets a chance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
